Finding aid for the Sylvia Plath collection MRBC.MS.00045
Mortimer Rare Book Collection
- Writings, 1949-1963; 1; 9.3 linear feet (17 boxes; 8 oversize folders)
  - Poetry, approximately 1950-2008; 5; 7.2 linear feet (12 boxes; 8 oversize folders)
    - Printed version of "Circus in Three Rings", August 1955 (Box 7, Folder 49, Item 3)
      Printed version from The Atlantic volume 196, number 2, page 68.
    - Photocopies of typescript of "City Streets" and letter to Hans Joachim Neupert, 1949 October 10 (Box 7, Folder 49.1)
      Photocopies of "City Streets" headed "Sylvia Plath Age 15 Wellesley, Mass." The poem is enclosed in a letter to Hans Joachim Neupert in which she discusses this and other enclosed poems: "The Stranger", "The Farewell", "White Phlox", and "Gone is the River."
    - Printed version of "The Colossus" (poem), 1962 April (Box 8, Folder 50)
      Printed version of the poem "The Colossus" from Encounter volume 18, page 56. "Encounter: April 1962" is written in Plath's hand at the top of the page.
    - Photocopies of typescripts for The Colossus (book), 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 51, Item 1)
      Photocopies of typescripts for Sylvia Plath's book The Colossus compiled from originals filed by the individual poem's title. The set is incomplete and some poems were taken from "The Bull of Bendylaw" typescript. Includes "The Beggars," "A Winter Ship," "Full Fathom Five," "Maudlin," "Blue Moles," "Strumpet Song," "Ouija," "Man in Black," "Snakecharmer," "The Hermit at Outermost House" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "The Disquieting Muses" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "Medallion" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "Two Sisters of Persephone" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "The Companionable Ills" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "Moonrise" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "Spinster" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "Frog Autumn" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"], "Ella Mason and Her Eleven Cats," "Mussel Hunter at Rock Harbor" [also with "The Bull of Bendylaw"]. "The Beggars" and "Ella Mason and Her Eleven Cats" omitted from final version.
      Originals are filed under the individual poem's title.
    - Preliminary materials for The Colossus (book), probably 1960; 6 pages (Box 8, Folder 51, Item 2)
      Typescript of preliminary materials for Sylvia Plath's book The Colossus including contents (2 pages), acknowledgements (2 pages), and a list of where and when poems were previously published (2 pages). Typescripts have handwritten annotations and underlining by Sylvia Plath.
    - Galley proofs for The Colossus (book), probably 1962; 32 pages (Box 8, Folder 51, Item 3)
      Galley proofs for Sylvia Plath's book The Colossus including handwritten corrections to "A Winter Ship" and "Man in Black."
    - Photocopies of page proofs for The Colossus (book), circa 1962 (Box 8, Folder 51, Item 4)
      Photocopies of page proofs for Sylvia Plath's book The Colossus with printer's annotations (possibly containing galley numbers).
    - Printed version of "The Companionable Ills", 1959 January 30 (Box 8, Folder 52, Item 1)
      Printed version from The Spectator volume 202, page 163.
    - Photocopy of typescript of "The Companionable Ills", 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 52, Item 2)
      Photocopy of a typescript of "The Companionable Ills" numbered 57, probably from Sylvia Plath's book The Colossus.
      Original with "Berck-Plage": Box 7, Folder 30, item 3.
    - Typescript of "Complaint", probably 1950 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      Typescript of "Complaint" annotated by Alfred Young Fisher. This poem is not published in Collected Poems.
    - Holograph of "Contusion", 1963 February 4 (Box 8, Folder 54, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Contusion" with Sylvia Plath's "Stings": item 10, page 1 on the back of the page.
    - Typescript of "Contusion", 1963 February 4; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 54, Item 2)
    - Typescript carbon of "Contusion", undated; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 54, Item 3)
    - Printed version of "Contusion", "Edge", "The Fearful", and "Kindness", 1963 February 17 (Box 8, Folder 54, Item 3)
      Photocopy of the printed version from Observer. Also includes "Edge", "The Fearful", and "Kindness", and the paragraph "A Poet's Epitaph" by A. Alvarez.
      Original filed with "Edge."
    - Typescript of "Conversation Among the Ruins", between 1957 September and 1958 September (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Holograph of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", October 2, probably 1962; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 56, Item 1)
      Holograph of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", variant title "The Courage of Quietness." The back of the pages have Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 6, pages 3 and 4.
    - Typescript of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", 1962 October 2; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 56, Item 2)
      Revised typescript (originals and carbon) of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", variant title "The Courage of Quietness."
    - Typescript of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", 1962 October 2; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 56, Item 3)
    - Typescript of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", 1962 October 2; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 56, Item 4)
      Revised typescript (originals and carbon) of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", variant title "The Courage of Quietness." The title on the carbon is changed to "The Courage of Shutting-Up."
    - Typescript of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", undated; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 56, Item 5)
      Corrected typescript with title "The Courage of Quietness" changed to "The Courage of Shutting-Up."
    - Photocopy of the printed version of "The Courage of Shutting-Up", "The Babysitters", "Pheasant", "Apprehensions", "For a Fatherless Son", and "By Candlelight", 1971 March 6 (Box 8, Folder 56, Item 6)
      Photocopy of the printed version from The New Yorker pages 36-37.
    - Holograph of "The Couriers", 1962 November 4; 1 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 57, Item 1)
    - Typescript carbon of "The Couriers", 1962 November 4; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 57, Item 2)
    - Revised typescript carbon of "The Couriers", undated; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 57, Item 3)
    - Typescript carbons of "The Couriers", 1962 November 4; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 57, Item 4)
    - Photocopy of the printed version of "The Couriers", "The Bee Meeting", "Stings", "Cut", "Letter in November", "Mary's Song", and "Years", 1963 April (Box 8, Folder 57, Item 5)
      Printed version from The London Magazine new series, volume 3, number 1, pages 30-21. The heading at the top of page 25 is "Seven Poems." Annotated by Aurelia Plath.
      Gift of Aurelia S. Plath, 1983.
    - Holograph of "Crossing the Water", undated; 1 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Crossing the Water", variant titles "Rock Lake at Night", and "Night Country." The back of the page has Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar early draft, chapter 4, page 17.
    - Holograph of "Crossing the Water", undated; 1 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 2)
      Revised holograph of "Crossing the Water", variant title "Rock Lake at Night", numbered 2 at the top of the page in Sylvia Plath's hand. The back of the page has Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar early draft, chapter 4, page 16.
    - Typescript of "Crossing the Water", undated; 1 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 3)
      Typescript of "Crossing the Water" numbered 3 at the top of the page in Sylvia Plath's hand. The back of the page has Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar early draft, chapter 4, page 15. Also includes preliminary notes for "Among the Narcissi."
    - Typescript of "Crossing the Water", 1962 April 14; 1 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 4)
      Revised typescript of "Crossing the Water", number 4 typed at the top of the page. The back of the page has Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar early draft, chapter 3, page 21.
    - Typescript carbon of "Crossing the Water", 1962 April 4; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 5)
      Corrected typescript carbon of "Crossing the Water" with "Observer" written at the top of the page in Sylvia Plath's hand and boxed in red pencil.
    - Typescript carbon of "Crossing the Water", undated; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 6)
      Typescript carbon of "Crossing the Water", double-spaced and corrected.
    - Typeset proof of "Crossing the Water", undated; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 7)
    - Printed version of "Crossing the Water", 1962 September 23 (Box 8, Folder 58, Item 8)
      Printed version from Observer September 23, 1962, page 25.
    - Typescript of "Crystal Gazer", between 1955 September and 1956 December (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Holograph of "Cut", 1962 October 24; 2 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 60, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Cut." The back of page 1 has Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 1, page 2 and the back of page 2 of the poem has chapter 2, page 10 of the same.
    - Typescript of "Cut", undated; 1 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 60, Item 2)
      Revised typescript of "Cut." The back of the page has Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 1, page 14.
    - Typescript of "Cut", undated; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 60, Item 3)
      Revised typescript (originals and carbons) of "Cut."
    - Typescript of "Cut", 1962 October 24; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 60, Item 4)
    - Photocopy of the printed version of "Cut", "The Bee Meeting", "Stings", "Letter in November", "The Couriers", "Mary's Song", and "Years", 1963 April (Box 8, Folder 60, Item 5)
      Photocopy of printed version from The London Magazine new series, volume 3, number 1, pages 28-29. The head of page 25 is "Seven Poems." Contains annotations by Aurelia Plath.
    - Holograph of "Daddy", undated; 3 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Daddy" with pages 4-6 of Ted Hughes' "The Calm" on the back of the pages.
    - Typescript of "Daddy", undated; 2 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 2)
      Revised typescript of "Daddy." The back of page 1 has page 3 of Ted Hughes' "The Calm." The back of page 2 has page 9 of Ted Hughes' "Review of Arnold Wesker."
    - Typescript of "Daddy", 1962 October 12; 2 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 3)
      Revised typescript of "Daddy" with a calculation of the number of lines written at the top of the page in Sylvia Plath's hand. The back of the pages have pages 7 and 8 of Ted Hughes' "Review of Arnold Wesker."
    - Page two of a typescript of "Daddy", undated; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 4)
      Page 2 (middle six stanzas) of a revised typescript of "Daddy", double-spaced.
    - Corrected typescript of "Daddy", 1962 October 12; 6 pages (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 5)
      Original and carbon corrected typescript of "Daddy."
    - Typescript of "Daddy", undated; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 6)
      Typescript carbons of "Daddy" double-spaced.
    - Photocopy of galley proofs for printed version of "Daddy", "Death & Co.", "The Swarm", "The Other", "Lady Lazarus", "Little Fugue", "Childless Woman", "The Jailor", "Thalidomide", and "Getting There", 1963 October 21 (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 7)
      Photocopy of galley proof from Encounter published as "Ten Poems."
    - Printed version of "Daddy", 1963 October (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 8)
      Printed version from Encounter volume XXI, number 4, page 52.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Daddy" and nine other poems by Sylvia Plath, 1963 October (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 9)
      Photocopy of printed version of "Daddy" from The Review (Oxford, England) number 9. Photocopy includes the cover and pages 4-19. The cover has the title "Sylvia Plath: The Last Poems" and pages include nine other poems by Plath in addition to "Daddy."
    - Printed version of "Daddy", 1964 (Box 8, Folder 61, Item 10)
      Printed version from New Poetry 1964: Critical Quarterly Poetry Supplement number 5, pages 2-4.
      Gift of Ann Safford Mandel, Smith College class of 1953, 10/21/1977.
    - Typescript of "Danse Macabre", 1955 February 10 (Box 8, Folder 62, Item 1)
      Typescript with annotations by Alfred Young Fisher. "For Alfred Young Fisher February 10, 1955" is typed on the reverse.
    - Photocopy of a printed version of "Danse Macabre" and the short story "Superman and Paula Brown's New Snowsuit", 1955 Spring (Box 8, Folder 62, Item 2)
      Photocopy of the printed version of the poem "Danse Macabre" and short story "Superman and Paula Brown's New Snowsuit" from Smith Review page 12. Cover includes annotations by Aurelia Plath and has "Sylvia Plath Lawrence" [House] written it Sylvia Plath's hand.
      Original with: Writings. Short Stories. "Superman and Paula Brown's New Snowsuit."
    - Printed version of "Danse Macabre", 1967 May (Box 8, Folder 62, Item 3)
      Printed version in The Harvard Advocate volume CI, number 1, page 2. One of seven "early poems" by Sylvia Plath, as well as two articles about her poetry by Elizabeth Aldrich and Stuart A. Davis. Annotation by Aurelia Plath.
    - Typescript of "Dark Wood, Dark Water", probably 1959 November (Box 8, Folder 63, Item 1)
      Typescript annotated and edited by Sylvia Plath. The first stanza is crossed out and a new stanza is written in the margin. "CS Monitor - revised version" is written at the top in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Typescript of "Dark Wood, Dark Water", undated (Box 8, Folder 63, Item 2)
      Typescript carbon numbered 27 by Sylvia Plath and revised in an unidentified hand.
    - Photocopy of the printed version of "Dark Wood, Dark Water", 1959 December 17 (Box 8, Folder 63, Item 3)
      Photocopy of the printed version from The Christian Science Monitor.
    - Holograph of "Death & Co.", undated; 2 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper, page 2 numbered in Sylvia Plath's hand. (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 1)
    - Typescript of "Death & Co.", undated; 1 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 2)
      Revised typescript numbered 3 in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Typescript of "Death & Co.", 1962 November 12; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 3)
      Revised typescript numbered 4 in Sylvia Plath's hand.
      Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper.
    - Photocopies of typescripts of "Death & Co.", undated; 4 pages (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 4)
      Photocopies of original and carbon typescripts of "Death & Co." on the backs of individual poems. Page 1 is on verso of "Totem": item 2, page 1. Page 2 is on the verso of "The Munich Mannequins": item 2, page 1. Page 3 is on the verso of "Child": item 2, page 1. Page 4 is on the verso of "Paralytic": item 2, page 2.
    - Typescript of page one of "Death & Co." and photocopies of pages two and three, 1962 November 12; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 5)
      Original typescript of page 1 and photocopies of typescripts of pages 2 and 3 of "Death & Co." Page 2 is on the verso of "The Munich Mannequins": item 1, page 2. Page 3 is on the verso of "Mystic": item 1, page 2.
    - Typescript and photocopies of typescripts of "Death & Co.", undated; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 6)
      Original and carbon typescripts of "Death & Co." revised. Two pages are originals and one page is a photocopy.
      Original of carbon 2 filed with item 10 in the "Death & Co." folder.
    - Typescript and photocopies of typescripts of "Death & Co.", 1962 November 14; 3 pages (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 7)
      Original and carbon typescripts of "Death & Co." revised. Page 1 is on the back of "Mystic": item 1, page 1. Page 3 is on the back of "Paralytic": item 2, page 3. One page is original and two pages are photocopies.
    - Holograph and typescript of "Death & Co.", undated; 2 pages; Typed and written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 8)
      Holograph and typescript of the last three stanzas of "Death & Co." revised.
    - Photocopy of typescript of "Death & Co.", undated; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 9)
      Photocopy of a typescript original and carbon of "Death & Co." The typescript is double-spaced and corrected. Page 1 is on the back of "Paralytic": item 3, page 1. Page 2 is on the back of "Gigolo": item 2, page 1.
    - Typescript of "Death & Co.", 1962 November 14; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 10)
      Typescript of "Death & Co." The back of the page is the corrected carbon typescript of the undated typescript of item 6 in this folder.
    - Typescript of "Death & Co.", 1962 November 14; 3 pages; Typescript original and carbons. (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 11)
    - Photocopy of galley proof of "Death & Co.", "Getting There", "The Swarm", "The Other", "Lady Lazarus", "Little Fugue", "Childless Woman", "The Jailor", "Thalidomide", and "Daddy", 1963 October 21 (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 12)
      Photocopy of galley proof for Encounter (21 Oct. 1963) published as "Ten Poems."
    - Printed version of "Death & Co." and nine other poems by Sylvia Plath, 1963 October (Box 8, Folder 64, Item 13)
      Printed version in Encounter volume XXI, number 4, page 45. Includes ten poems by Sylvia Plath and a note by Ted Hughes about the poems. Annotations are by Aurelia Plath.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Denouement" and "Admonition", 1954 Spring (Box 8, Folder 64.1)
      Photocopy of printed version in Smith Review page 23, 1954 Spring. "Sylvia Plath" is written on the cover in her own hand in addition to annotations by Aurelia Plath.
      Original filed with "Warning."
    - Printed version of "Departure", 1959 March 7 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      Two copies of printed version from The Nation volume 188, page 212.
    - Typescript of "Desert Song", 1955 April 21 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      Typescript with annotations by Alfred Young Fisher. "Sylvia Plath April 21, 1955, For Mr. Fisher" is typed on the back of the page in addition to Sylvia Plath's handwritten annotation: "[Springfield, MA?] Union page 30 Friday April 29".
    - Holograph of "The Detective", 1962 October 1; 2 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 67, Item 1)
      Holograph of "The Detective", variant title "The Mill Stones", numbered 1 and 2 by Sylvia Plath. The back of page 1 is Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 5, page 12. The back of page 2 is chapter 5, page 3 of the same.
    - Typescript of "The Detective", 1962 October 1; 1 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 67, Item 2)
      Revised typescript of "The Detective" with Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 5, page 4 on the back of the page.
    - Typescript of "The Detective", 1962 October 1; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 67, Item 3)
      Revised typescript (original and carbon) of "The Detective."
    - Typescript of "The Detective", 1962 October 1; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 67, Item 4)
      Typescript (original and carbon) of "The Detective."
    - Typescript of "The Detective", undated; 1 pages (Box 8, Folder 67, Item 5)
    - Typescript of "Dialogue Between Ghost and Priest", not before 1953 April (Box 8, Folder 68)
      Typescript corrected and revised by Sylvia Plath.
    - Typescript carbon of "Dialogue en Route", between 1955 September and 1956 December (Box 8, Folder 69, Item 1)
    - Printed version of "Dialogue en Route", 1955 January (Box 8, Folder 69, Item 2)
      Printed version in Smith Review: Exam Blues Issue 1955 January, pages 12-12. The cover and contents page are annotated by Aurelia Plath.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Dialogue en Route", 1967 May (Box 8, Folder 69, Item 3)
      Photocopy of a printed version of "Dialogue en Route" from The Harvard Advocate volume CI, number 1, page 3. One of seven "early poems" by Sylvia Plath, as well as two articles about her poetry by Elizabeth Aldrich and Stuart A. Davis. Annotations are by Aurelia Plath.
    - Typescript of "Dirge in Three Parts", undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
      Typescript carbon of "Dirge in Three Parts." This poem is not printed in Collected Poems
    - Typescript of "The Dispossessed", between 1957 September and 1958 September (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Typeset proof of "The Disquieting Muses", 1958 or 1959; 2 pages (Box 8, Folder 72, Item 1)
      Typeset proof with editor's corrections. The second page is headed "Guinness Book of Poetry--Book III--26". "The Disquieting Muses" was published in the Guinness Book of Poetry 1958-1959.
    - Photocopy of typescript of "The Disquieting Muses" (Box 8, Folder 72, Item 2)
      Photocopy of a typescript of "The Disquieting Muses" numbered 50-52, probably from the book The Colossus [1959-1960]. The back of the page has "Berck-Plage": item 3, 1962 June 30.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "The Disquieting Muses", "Snakecharmer", and "Lorelei", 1959 March (Box 8, Folder 72, Item 3)
      Photocopy of printed version from The London Magazine volume 6, pages 33-36. Annotations are by Sylvia Plath.
      Original filed with "Snakecharmer."
    - Typescript of "Doomsday", probably 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 73, Item 1)
      Typescript carbon of "Doomsday." The page is numbered 59, probably from the book "Two Lovers and a Beachcomber."
    - Photocopy of a printed version of "Doomsday", "Eva Descending the Stair" and "Mad Girl's Love Song", 1953 Spring (Box 8, Folder 73, Item 2)
      Photocopy of printed version in Smith Review with heading "Two Villanelles", page 22. "Sylvia Plath" is written in her own hand on the front cover. The cover is also annotated by Aurelia Plath.
    - Printed version of "Doomsday", 1954 May (Box 8, Folder 73, Item 3)
      Printed version of "Doomsday" in Harper's volume 208, page 29. Sylvia Plath's signature in on the front cover along with manuscript annotations by Aurelia Plath.
    - Photocopy of a printed version of "Doomsday", 1967 May (Box 8, Folder 73, Item 4)
      Photocopy of printed version of "Doomsday" from The Harvard Advocate volume CI, number 1, page 2. One of seven "early poems" by Sylvia Plath as well as two articles about her poetry by Elizabeth Aldrich and Stuart A. Davis. Annotations are by Aurelia Plath.
    - Typescript of "The Dream", probably 1955 (Box 8, Folder 74, Item 1)
      Typescript of "The Dream" annotated by Alfred Young Fisher.
    - Typescript of "The Dream", between 1957 December and 1958 December (Box 8, Folder 74, Item 2)
    - Typescript of "Dream with Clam-diggers", between 1955 September and 1956 December (Box 8, Folder 75, Item 1)
      Typescript carbon of "Dream with Clam-diggers" with annotations by Sylvia Plath. "Sold - Poetry - Oct. 1956" is annotated at the top of the page in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Typescript of "Dream with Clam-diggers" (Box 8, Folder 75, Item 2)
      Typescript carbon of "Dream with Clam-diggers." The page is numbered 48, probably from the book "Two Lovers and a Beachcomber", [1956-1957].
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Dream with Clam-diggers", 1957 Janurary (Box 8, Folder 75, Item 3)
      Photocopy of printed version from Poetry volume 88, page 232.
    - Holograph of "Eavesdropper", 1962 October 13; 5 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 76, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Eavesdropper" numbered 1-5 by Sylvia Plath. Eight lines of unidentified typescript are upside down at the bottom of page 2. The backs of pages 1-5 have Ted Hughes. Review of Arnold Wesker, pages 2-6.
    - Incomplete typescript of "Eavesdropper", undated; 1 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 8, Folder 76, Item 2)
      Typescript of part of the first stanza of "Eavesdropper." The page is annotated at the top in Sylvia Plath's hand,"The Nation." The back of the page is Ted Hughes. Review of Arnold Wesker, page [1].